<metadata>
  <idinfo>
    <citation>
      <citeinfo>
        <title>CHTEXTURE</title>
        <geoform>tabular digital data</geoform>
      </citeinfo>
    </citation>
    <descript>
      <abstract>The Horizon Texture table lists the individual texture(s), or term(s) used in lieu of texture, for the referenced horizon. Only the unmodified texture terms are listed in the Horizon Texture table; modifiers are listed in the Horizon Texture Modifier table. For example, a gravelly loamy sand is shown as "GR-LS" in the Horizon Texture Group table, "ls" in the Horizon Texture table, and "gr" in the Horizon Texture Modifier table.</abstract>
      <purpose>Horizon Texture Table</purpose>
    </descript>
    <accconst>None</accconst>
    <useconst>None</useconst>
    <native>Microsoft Windows 7 Version 6.1 (Build 7601) Service Pack 1; Esri ArcGIS 10.1.1.3143</native>
  </idinfo>
  <eainfo>
    <detailed>
      <enttyp>
        <enttypl>chtexture</enttypl>
      </enttyp>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>chtkey</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>A non-connotative string of characters used to uniquely identify a record in the Horizon Texture table.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>lieutex</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Substitute terms applied to materials that do not fit into a textural class because of organic matter content, size, rupture resistance, solubility, or another reason.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>chtgkey</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The unique identifier of a record in the Horizon Texture Group table. Use this column to join the Horizon Texture table to the Horizon Texture Group table.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>texcl</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>An expression, based on the USDA system of particle sizes, for the relative portions of the various size groups of individual mineral grains less than 2mm equivalent diameter in a mass of soil.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Internal feature number.</attrdef>
        <attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs>
        <attrdomv>
          <udom>Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom>
        </attrdomv>
      </attr>
    </detailed>
  </eainfo>
  <metainfo>
    <metd>20131230</metd>
    <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
    <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
    <mettc>local time</mettc>
  </metainfo>
</metadata>