<metadata>
  <idinfo>
    <citation>
      <citeinfo>
        <title>COEPLANTS</title>
        <geoform>tabular digital data</geoform>
      </citeinfo>
    </citation>
    <descript>
      <abstract>The Component Existing Plants table lists the plants, either rangeland or forestland plants, that typically occur on the referenced map unit component.</abstract>
      <purpose>Component Existing Plants Table</purpose>
    </descript>
    <accconst>None</accconst>
    <useconst>None</useconst>
    <native>Microsoft Windows 7 Version 6.1 (Build 7601) Service Pack 1; Esri ArcGIS 10.1.1.3143</native>
  </idinfo>
  <eainfo>
    <detailed>
      <enttyp>
        <enttypl>coeplants</enttypl>
      </enttyp>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Internal feature number.</attrdef>
        <attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs>
        <attrdomv>
          <udom>Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom>
        </attrdomv>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>coeplantskey</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>A non-connotative string of characters used to uniquely identify a record in the Component Existing Plants table.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>rangeprod</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The percentage of total annual site production attributed to the specific rangeland plant, expressed as percent of total air dry plant material by weight.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>cokey</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The unique identifier of a record in the Component table. Use this column to join the Component Existing Plants table to the Component table.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>forestunprod</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The percentage of total annual site production attributed to the specific forest understory plant, expressed as percent of total air dry plant material by weight.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>plantsym</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>A unique symbol used to identify a plant genus or a plant species. (The PLANTS Database, USDA-NRCS, National Plant Data Center.)</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>plantsciname</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The full genus and species name as listed in the PLANTS Database, USDA-NRCS, National Plant Data Center.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>plantcomname</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>A generally accepted common name used for a plant in a geographic region, usually a state.</attrdef>
      </attr>
    </detailed>
  </eainfo>
  <metainfo>
    <metd>20131230</metd>
    <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
    <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
    <mettc>local time</mettc>
  </metainfo>
</metadata>