<metadata>
  <idinfo>
    <citation>
      <citeinfo>
        <title>COPM</title>
        <geoform>tabular digital data</geoform>
      </citeinfo>
    </citation>
    <descript>
      <abstract>The Component Parent Material table lists the individual parent material(s) for the referenced map unit component. In some cases where soils developed in multiple materials in a vertical sequence, that sequence will be noted. In other cases multiple entries with no vertical sequence noted indicates the soil may have formed in one of the materials listed.</abstract>
      <purpose>Component Parent Material Table</purpose>
    </descript>
    <accconst>None</accconst>
    <useconst>None</useconst>
    <native>Microsoft Windows 7 Version 6.1 (Build 7601) Service Pack 1; Esri ArcGIS 10.1.1.3143</native>
  </idinfo>
  <eainfo>
    <detailed>
      <enttyp>
        <enttypl>copm</enttypl>
      </enttyp>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Internal feature number.</attrdef>
        <attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs>
        <attrdomv>
          <udom>Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom>
        </attrdomv>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>copmkey</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>A non-connotative string of characters used to uniquely identify a record in the Component Parent Material table.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>pmorigin</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The type of bedrock from which the parent material was derived.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>copmgrpkey</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The unique identifier of a record in the Component Parent Material Group table. Use this column to join the Component Parent Material Group table to the Component Parent Material table.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>pmkind</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>A term describing the general physical, chemical and mineralogical composition of the material, mineral or organic, from which the soil develops. Mode of deposition and/or weathering may be implied or implicit.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>pmorder</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The sequence in which the parent material occurs, when more than one parent material exists for one soil profile. If only one parent material occurs for a soil, i.e. no lithologic discontinuities, no entry is required.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>pmmodifier</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>General description of the texture of the parent material. Class limits correspond to those of textural groupings defined in the Soil Survey Manual and family particle-size classes in Soil Taxonomy.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>pmgenmod</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>A user specified term(s) used to further describe the nature of the parent material for a given soil.</attrdef>
      </attr>
    </detailed>
  </eainfo>
  <metainfo>
    <metd>20131230</metd>
    <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
    <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
    <mettc>local time</mettc>
  </metainfo>
</metadata>