<metadata>
  <idinfo>
    <citation>
      <citeinfo>
        <title>MAPUNIT</title>
        <geoform>tabular digital data</geoform>
      </citeinfo>
    </citation>
    <descript>
      <abstract>The Mapunit table identifies the map units included in the referenced legend. Data related the map unit as a whole are also given.</abstract>
      <purpose>Mapunit Table</purpose>
    </descript>
    <accconst>None</accconst>
    <useconst>None</useconst>
    <native>Microsoft Windows 7 Version 6.1 (Build 7601) Service Pack 1; Esri ArcGIS 10.1.1.3143</native>
  </idinfo>
  <eainfo>
    <detailed>
      <enttyp>
        <enttypl>mapunit</enttypl>
      </enttyp>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>mapunitlfw_r</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The approximate width of a particular map unit delineation represented by a linear soil feature on a soil map.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>mustatus</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Identifies the current status of the map unit. As of SSURGO version 2.1, values for this attribute are no longer provided. This attribute will be dropped from the next major SSURGO version.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>muacres</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The number of acres of a particular map unit within the geographic area to which the legend applies. The number listed here may differ from that measured using GIS software due to different measuring techniques and rounding practices, or due to the fact that the value has been adjusted so that the sum total of all map units in the legend equals that listed for soil survey area.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>mukind</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Code identifying the kind of mapunit. Example: C - consociation.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>interpfocus</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The targeted landuse for which the Map Unit was developed. The properties of included mapunit components are tailored towards this landuse.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>invesintens</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The level of detail and relative intensity of field observation under which the map unit was developed. Order 1 indicates the highest intensity, and order 5 the lowest.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>muwathelcl</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The Highly Erodible Lands (HEL) classification for the mapunit based on the rating of its components for water HEL classification.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>muhelcl</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The overall Highly Erodible Lands (HEL) classification for the mapunit based on the rating of its components for wind and water HEL classification.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>mapunitpfa_h</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The approximate area of a particular map unit delineation represented by a point feature on a soil map.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>mukey</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>A non-connotative string of characters used to uniquely identify a record in the Mapunit table.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>mucertstat</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The level of certification assigned to a map unit. Intended to indicate whether or not the map unit should be used and the degree of confidence with which it may be used. As of SSURGO version 2.1, values for this attribute are no longer provided. This attribute will be dropped from the next major SSURGO version.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>lkey</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The unique identifier of a record in the Legend table. Use this column to join the Mapunit table to the Legend table.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>vtsepticsyscl</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The interpretive separations, or class, based on the ability of the map unit to support an onsite septic system. (Ancillary Soil Interpretation Ratings For On-site Sewerage Disposal in Vermont)</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>iacornsr</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Corn Suitability Rating (CSR) is an index procedure developed in Iowa to rate each different kind of soil for its row-crop productivity.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>nhiforsoigrp</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Interpretative class for the map unit, based on NH developed interpretations.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>musym</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The symbol used to uniquely identify the soil mapunit in the soil survey.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>mapunitpfa_l</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The approximate area of a particular map unit delineation represented by a point feature on a soil map.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>muwndhelcl</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The Highly Erodible Lands (HEL) classification for the mapunit based on the rating of its components for wind HEL classification.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Internal feature number.</attrdef>
        <attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs>
        <attrdomv>
          <udom>Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom>
        </attrdomv>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>mapunitlfw_h</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The approximate width of a particular map unit delineation represented by a linear soil feature on a soil map.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>mapunitlfw_l</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The approximate width of a particular map unit delineation represented by a linear soil feature on a soil map.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>muname</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Correlated name of the mapunit (recommended name or field name for surveys in progress).</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>farmlndcl</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Identification of map units as prime farmland, farmland of statewide importance, or farmland of local importance.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>mapunitpfa_r</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The approximate area of a particular map unit delineation represented by a point feature on a soil map.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>nhspiagr</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>New Hampshire Soil Potential Index for Agriculture, 1992 revision. Used for computation of weighted average SPI on a parcel of land for adjustment of current use land assessment.</attrdef>
      </attr>
    </detailed>
  </eainfo>
  <metainfo>
    <metd>20131230</metd>
    <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
    <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
    <mettc>local time</mettc>
  </metainfo>
</metadata>