<metadata>
  <idinfo>
    <citation>
      <citeinfo>
        <title>MDSTATDOMMAS</title>
        <geoform>tabular digital data</geoform>
      </citeinfo>
    </citation>
    <descript>
      <abstract>The Domain Master Static Metadata table records the metadata that pertains to a domain as a whole, for all domains associated with the tabular data set. A domain is a fixed set of choices to which a column's value is restricted. Each column in the Table Column Static Metadata table whose logical data type is "choice", has a corresponding domain. Each record in this table represents a particular domain. A particular domain may serve as the domain for more than one column. Information about the members that make up a particular domain is found in the Domain Detail Static Metadata table.</abstract>
      <purpose>Domain Master Static Metadata Table</purpose>
    </descript>
    <accconst>None</accconst>
    <useconst>None</useconst>
    <native>Microsoft Windows 7 Version 6.1 (Build 7601) Service Pack 1; Esri ArcGIS 10.1.1.3143</native>
  </idinfo>
  <eainfo>
    <detailed>
      <enttyp>
        <enttypl>mdstatdommas</enttypl>
      </enttyp>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>domainmaxlen</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The number of characters in the longest member of a domain. Each member of a domain is an ASCII character string consisting of at least 1 but no more than 254 characters.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Internal feature number.</attrdef>
        <attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs>
        <attrdomv>
          <udom>Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom>
        </attrdomv>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>domainname</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The name of the domain to which a column's values are restricted. A domain is a finite list of character strings that a column's value may assume.</attrdef>
      </attr>
    </detailed>
  </eainfo>
  <metainfo>
    <metd>20131230</metd>
    <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
    <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
    <mettc>local time</mettc>
  </metainfo>
</metadata>