<metadata>
  <idinfo>
    <citation>
      <citeinfo>
        <title>MDSTATTABS</title>
        <geoform>tabular digital data</geoform>
      </citeinfo>
    </citation>
    <descript>
      <abstract>The Table Static Metadata table records metadata about the tables that make up the tabular data set. Each record in this table represents one table.</abstract>
      <purpose>Table Static Metadata Table</purpose>
    </descript>
    <accconst>None</accconst>
    <useconst>None</useconst>
    <native>Microsoft Windows 7 Version 6.1 (Build 7601) Service Pack 1; Esri ArcGIS 10.1.1.3143</native>
  </idinfo>
  <eainfo>
    <detailed>
      <enttyp>
        <enttypl>mdstattabs</enttypl>
      </enttyp>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>iefilename</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The base part of the file name of a table's associated ASCII pipe delimited import/export file. The complete name of a table's associated import/export file is the base name followed by the characters ".txt". For example, if the base name is "alpha", the name of the associated import/export file is "alpha.txt".</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>tablabel</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>A descriptive label associated with a database table. For SSURGO, every table's label must be unique, making a table's label a suitable alias for identifying a table. For SSURGO, table labels are typically mixed case character strings with embedded blanks.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>tabdesc</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>A narrative text description of what a database table represents or records.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>tablogname</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>A name associated with a database table that is more connotative than the table's corresponding physical name. For SSURGO, every table's logical name must be unique, making a table's logical name a suitable alias for identifying a table. For SSURGO, table logical names are lower case character strings with no embedded blanks, where individual parts of the logical name may be separated using the underscore character.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Internal feature number.</attrdef>
        <attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs>
        <attrdomv>
          <udom>Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom>
        </attrdomv>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>tabphyname</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The name that is used to physically implement a table in a database management system. In a database, each table's physical name must be unique.</attrdef>
      </attr>
    </detailed>
  </eainfo>
  <metainfo>
    <metd>20131230</metd>
    <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
    <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
    <mettc>local time</mettc>
  </metainfo>
</metadata>