<metadata>
  <idinfo>
    <citation>
      <citeinfo>
        <title>MDSTATRSHIPDET</title>
        <geoform>tabular digital data</geoform>
      </citeinfo>
    </citation>
    <descript>
      <abstract>The Relationship Detail Static Metadata table records the pairs of join columns that define a particular relationship. Each record in this table represents one pair of join columns for a particular relationship.</abstract>
      <purpose>Relationship Detail Static Metadata Table</purpose>
    </descript>
    <accconst>None</accconst>
    <useconst>None</useconst>
    <native>Microsoft Windows 7 Version 6.1 (Build 7601) Service Pack 1; Esri ArcGIS 10.1.1.3143</native>
  </idinfo>
  <eainfo>
    <detailed>
      <enttyp>
        <enttypl>mdstatrshipdet</enttypl>
      </enttyp>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>rtabcolphyname</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The physical name of a column of a table on the right side of a relationship between two tables. This column is one of several potential columns used to create a join between the two tables involved in a relationship. The right table column joins to its corresponding left table column.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>relationshipname</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>A name given to a relationship between two tables. If there is more than one relationship between the same two tables, the name of each of those relationships must be unique.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>ltabcolphyname</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The physical name of a column of a table on the left side of a relationship between two tables. This column is one of several potential columns used to create a join between the two tables involved in a relationship. The left table column joins to its corresponding right table column.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>rtabphyname</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The physical name of a table on the right side of a relationship between two tables.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Internal feature number.</attrdef>
        <attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs>
        <attrdomv>
          <udom>Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom>
        </attrdomv>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>ltabphyname</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The physical name of a table on the left side of a relationship between two tables.</attrdef>
      </attr>
    </detailed>
  </eainfo>
  <metainfo>
    <metd>20131230</metd>
    <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
    <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
    <mettc>local time</mettc>
  </metainfo>
</metadata>