<metadata>
  <idinfo>
    <citation>
      <citeinfo>
        <title>MUAGGATT</title>
        <geoform>tabular digital data</geoform>
      </citeinfo>
    </citation>
    <descript>
      <abstract>The Mapunit Aggregated Attribute table records a variety of soil attributes and interpretations that have been aggregated from the component level to a single value at the map unit level. They have been aggregated by one or more appropriate means in order to express a consolidated value or interpretation for the map unit as a whole.</abstract>
      <purpose>Mapunit Aggregated Attribute Table</purpose>
    </descript>
    <accconst>None</accconst>
    <useconst>None</useconst>
    <native>Microsoft Windows 7 Version 6.1 (Build 7601) Service Pack 1; Esri ArcGIS 10.1.1.3143</native>
  </idinfo>
  <eainfo>
    <detailed>
      <enttyp>
        <enttypl>muaggatt</enttypl>
      </enttyp>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>aws0100wta</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Available water storage (AWS). The volume of water that the soil, to a depth of 100 centimeters, can store that is available to plants. It is reported as the weighted average of all components in the map unit, and is expressed as centimeters of water. AWS is calculated from AWC (available water capacity) which is commonly estimated as the difference between the water contents at 1/10 or 1/3 bar (field capacity) and 15 bars (permanent wilting point) tension, and adjusted for salinity and fragments.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>aws025wta</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Available water storage (AWS). The volume of water that the soil, to a depth of 25 centimeters, can store that is available to plants. It is reported as the weighted average of all components in the map unit, and is expressed as centimeters of water. AWS is calculated from AWC (available water capacity) which is commonly estimated as the difference between the water contents at 1/10 or 1/3 bar (field capacity) and 15 bars (permanent wilting point) tension, and adjusted for salinity and fragments.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>pondfreqprs</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The percentage of the map unit that is subject to water being ponded on the soil surface, expressed as one of four classes; 0-14%, 15-49%, 50-74% or 75-100%.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>flodfreqdcd</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The annual probability of a flood event expressed as a class. This column displays the dominant flood frequency class for the map unit, based on composition percentage of map unit components whose composition in the map unit is equal to or exceeds 15%.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>iccdcdpct</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The percent composition of the map unit that has the capability class displayed in the Irrigated Capability Class</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>wtdepannmin</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The shallowest depth to a wet soil layer (water table) at any time during the year expressed as centimeters from the soil surface, for components whose composition in the map unit is equal to or exceeds 15%.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>engdwobdcd</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The rating of the map unit as a site for dwellings without basements, expressed as the dominant rating class for the map unit, based on composition percentage of each map unit component.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>niccdcd</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The broadest category in the land capability classification system for soils. This column displays the dominant capability class, under non-irrigated conditions, for the map unit based on composition percentage of all components in the map unit.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>iccdcd</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The broadest category in the land capability classification system for soils. This column displays the dominant capability class, under irrigated conditions, for the map unit based on composition percentage of all components in the map unit.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>englrsdcd</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The rating of the map unit as a site for local roads and streets, expressed as the dominant rating class for the map unit, based on composition percentage of each map unit component.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>engcmssdcd</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The rating of the map unit as a source of sand, expressed as the dominant class for the map unit, based on composition percentage of each map unit component.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>engsldcd</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The rating of the map unit as a site for sewage lagoons, expressed as the dominant rating class for the map unit, based on composition percentage of each map unit component.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>engstafml</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The rating of the map unit as a site for septic tank absorption fields, expressed as the most limiting rating class for the map unit, based on the evaluation of each component in the map unit.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>engstafdcd</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The rating of the map unit as a site for septic tank absorption fields, expressed as the dominant rating class for the map unit, based on composition percentage of each map unit component.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>mukey</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The unique identifier of a record in the Mapunit table. It also serves as the non-connotative string of characters used to uniquely identify a record in the Mapunit Aggregated Attribute table as there is a one-to-one relationship between records in these two tables. Use this column to join the Mapunit Aggregated Attribute table to the Mapunit table.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>hydclprs</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>An indication of the proportion of the map unit, expressed as a class, that is "hydric", based on the hydric classification of individual map unit components.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>awmmfpwwta</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The relative rating of the map unit for use as a disposal site of Manure and Food Processing Wastes, expressed as a weighted average of numerical ratings for individual components in the map unit. The ratings are on a scale of 0.0 to 1.0, with the higher values indicating increasing limitations.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>forpehrtdcp</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The relative potential erosion hazard for the map unit when used as a site for forest roads and trails, expressed as the rating class for the dominant component in the map unit, based on composition percentage of each map unit component.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>engcmssmp</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The rating of the map unit as a source of sand, expressed as the most probable class for the map unit, based on the evaluation of each component whose composition in the map unit is equal to or exceeds 15%.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>aws0150wta</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Available water storage (AWS). The volume of water that the soil, to a depth of 150 centimeters, can store that is available to plants. It is reported as the weighted average of all components in the map unit, and is expressed as centimeters of water. AWS is calculated from AWC (available water capacity) which is commonly estimated as the difference between the water contents at 1/10 or 1/3 bar (field capacity) and 15 bars (permanent wilting point) tension, and adjusted for salinity and fragments.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>urbrecptdcd</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The rating of the map unit as a site for paths and trails, expressed as the dominant rating class for the map unit, based on composition percentage of each map unit component.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>aws050wta</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Available water storage (AWS). The volume of water that the soil, to a depth of 50 centimeters, can store that is available to plants. It is reported as the weighted average of all components in the map unit, and is expressed as centimeters of water. AWS is calculated from AWC (available water capacity) which is commonly estimated as the difference between the water contents at 1/10 or 1/3 bar (field capacity) and 15 bars (permanent wilting point) tension, and adjusted for salinity and fragments.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>slopegradwta</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The difference is elevation between two points, expressed as a percentage of the distance between those points. This column displays the weighted average slope gradient of all components in the map unit.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>brockdepmin</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The distance from the soil surface to the top of a bedrock layer, expressed as a shallowest depth of components whose composition in the map unit is equal to or exceeds 15%.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>mustatus</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Identifies the current status of the map unit. As of SSURGO version 2.1, values for this attribute are no longer provided. This attribute will be dropped from the next major SSURGO version.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>drclasswettest</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The natural drainage condition of the soil refers to the frequency and duration of wet periods. This column displays the wettest drainage class assigned to an individual component of the map unit whose composition in the map unit is equal to or exceeds 15%.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>wtdepaprjunmin</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The shallowest depth to a wet soil layer (water table) during the months of April through June expressed in centimeters from the soil surface for components whose composition in the map unit is equal to or exceeds 15%.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Internal feature number.</attrdef>
        <attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs>
        <attrdomv>
          <udom>Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom>
        </attrdomv>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>engdwbll</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The rating of the map unit as a site for dwellings with basements, expressed as the least limiting rating class for the map unit, based on the evaluation of each component in the map unit.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>engsldcp</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The rating of the map unit as a site for sewage lagoons, expressed as the rating class for the dominant component in the map unit, based on composition percentage of each map unit component.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>drclassdcd</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The natural drainage condition of the soil refers to the frequency and duration of wet periods. This column displays the dominant drainage class for the map unit, based on composition percentage of each map unit component.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>flodfreqmax</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The annual probability of a flood event expressed as a class. This column displays the highest probability class assigned to an individual component of the map unit whose composition in the map unit is equal to or exceeds 15%.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>muname</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Correlated name of the mapunit (recommended name or field name for surveys in progress).</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>slopegraddcp</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The difference is elevation between two points, expressed as a percentage of the distance between those points. This column displays the slope gradient of the dominant component of the map unit based on composition percentage.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>engdwbdcd</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The rating of the map unit as a site for dwellings with basements, expressed as the dominant rating class for the map unit, based on composition percentage of each map unit component.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>niccdcdpct</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The percent composition of the map unit that has the capability class displayed in the Non-Irrigated Capability Class - Dominant Condition column.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>hydgrpdcd</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Hydrologic Group is a grouping of soils that have similar runoff potential under similar storm and cover conditions. This column displays the dominant hydrologic group for the map unit, based on composition percentage of each map unit component.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>engstafll</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The rating of the map unit as a site for septic tank absorption fields, expressed as the least limiting rating class for the map unit, based on the evaluation of each component in the map unit.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>engdwbml</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The rating of the map unit as a site for dwellings with basements, expressed as the most limiting rating class for the map unit, based on the evaluation of each component in the map unit.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>urbrecptwta</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The relative rating of the map unit for use as paths and trails, expressed as a weighted average of numerical ratings for individual soil components in the map unit. The ratings are on a scale of 0.0 to 1.0, with the higher values indicating more limitations.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>musym</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The symbol used to uniquely identify the soil mapunit in the soil survey.</attrdef>
      </attr>
    </detailed>
  </eainfo>
  <metainfo>
    <metd>20131230</metd>
    <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
    <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
    <mettc>local time</mettc>
  </metainfo>
</metadata>