<metadata>
  <idinfo>
    <citation>
      <citeinfo>
        <title>MUTEXT</title>
        <geoform>tabular digital data</geoform>
      </citeinfo>
    </citation>
    <descript>
      <abstract>The Mapunit Text table contains notes and narrative descriptions related to the referenced map unit.</abstract>
      <purpose>Mapunit Text Table</purpose>
    </descript>
    <accconst>None</accconst>
    <useconst>None</useconst>
    <native>Microsoft Windows 7 Version 6.1 (Build 7601) Service Pack 1; Esri ArcGIS 10.1.1.3143</native>
  </idinfo>
  <eainfo>
    <detailed>
      <enttyp>
        <enttypl>mutext</enttypl>
      </enttyp>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Internal feature number.</attrdef>
        <attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs>
        <attrdomv>
          <udom>Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom>
        </attrdomv>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>mutextkey</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>A non-connotative string of characters used to uniquely identify a record in the Mapunit Text table.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>text</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The actual narrative text portion of a text entry. The other parts of a text entry are its identifiers: kind, category and subcategory.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>mukey</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The unique identifier of a record in the Mapunit table. Use this column to join the Mapunit Text table to the Mapunit table.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>textsubcat</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>A text entry is identified by its kind, category, and subcategory. Subcategory is a subdivision of category. For text kind "Nontechnical" description and text category "Agr", subcategory would correspond to the SSSD field "desnum".</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>recdate</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>The date associated with a particular record, expressed as month, day, year -- xx/xx/xxxx.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>mapunittextkind</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>Text kind provides a grouping of text entries according to their subject matter. For example, the text kind "edit notes" groups text entries that deal with adding or changing data.</attrdef>
      </attr>
      <attr>
        <attrlabl>textcat</attrlabl>
        <attrdef>A text entry is identified by its kind, category, and subcategory. Category is a subdivision of kind. "Agr" and "Soi" are two categories for the text kind "Nontechnical Description".</attrdef>
      </attr>
    </detailed>
  </eainfo>
  <metainfo>
    <metd>20131230</metd>
    <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
    <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
    <mettc>local time</mettc>
  </metainfo>
</metadata>